The majority of people that
are trying to make money online
and get new clients all
share the same bottleneck in their sales
process.
And in this video,
I'm going to share with you how a sheet of
paper that literally
cost me 19p generated me $23,000
in revenue in the last three days. Now,
this is the bit where people
show their Stripe account. Oh, it's a lie.
It's now at 24K. Much of social media,
growing a following, actually, every
single part of the business
is about spotting patterns,
and I found one.
I, yes, started using RevTrack, which
is Ed Lawrence's new bit of software
that shows me where my clicks
are getting attributed to.
And we still haven't set it up properly,
even though I've been using it for months.
But the one thing I want you to see here
is, if I look for where the most
clicks are coming from, you will see here,
landing page.
Therefore, I now know that
when I make content about
landing pages, people seem to click,
which is good.
So then I decided to make a lead magnet.
However, every lead magnet
that I have leans upon heavily
email automations. I'll show you one.
Because I like to automate a sales
process, and although some people love
doing sales calls, and that's great,
I refuse to talk to
anyone before they have given me their
money.
And I know that can sound like a pretty
much of a prick thing to say, but that's
just how it is.
I don't want to do a sales call.
I don't want to deal with you unless your
money is in my bank account.
And I think that's okay,
because guess what?
I have a very finite social battery.
And the amount of sales calls I've done in
my business is zero, niche,
nil, and it will always be that way.
So here you can see a long list of emails
that I've pre-written in the fitness
industry, which means that basically,
when I sign someone up to this, they've
got a PhD and level three PT come the end
of it.
And if they haven't bought by the end of
that automation, I can't help them.
So I needed to make a lead magnet,
and I was thinking to myself,
[inhales] asking
for people's email addresses just feels a
bit rinsed.
So I went away and I put together an asset
which I called the
anatomy of a highly efficient sales page.
Now, here's the thing.
I've been roasting people in the Discord
this morning, and this is the common trend
that they all have.
If I could take what you are trying to get
people to sign up to and I
was to put it on a sign
and hold it in the high street,
no one would care. 17 tips. Fuck off,
mate. Get out the way.
14 ways in 14 days. Fuck off. Big issue.
No, thanks.
Be a better version of yourself.
Fuck off with your shitty lead magnets.
14 mobility hacks. Fuck off, mate.
But I honestly believe that
if I could get every single one of you to
walk down the
high street and I was to say, "Hey, guys,
here's the anatomy of a highly efficient
sales page.
Do you want a copy?" The majority of you
would go, "Yeah, I would
actually." And this
is actually the formula
that I'm a big fan of.
Obviously, you can't read that,
and I'm keeping it arm's length,
so you have to
click the link in the description.
Here's the mad thing.
I teach you the things
that work for me because they'll work for
you.
And when you click on the link in the
description, isn't it crazy?
That's going to come up on my RevTrack.
Wow.
And listen, you plebs,
I got a graphic designer to put
that together.
Do you know why? Because
if I tried doing this myself,
it's going to look fucking
shit. And if a graphic designer does it,
oh, but that might cost
£45.
This potentially... Actually, no,
not potentially.
This has made me tens of thousands of
dollars in three fucking days.
Do you think I'm bothered about the £45 it
costs to get a graphic designer to do
it? No.
So then I didn't just have a verbal call
to action.
I had a physical asset
that I could have as a lead magnet to perk
curiosity that I guarantee
that the majority of people in my captive
audience
that want or potentially could do business
with me would be interested in.
There's the way you temperature test it.
If you held the sign in the high street,
would people give a shit?
If yes, make it. If no, work on it. Now,
I'm coming with
receipts, brother. Here's my ManyChat,
which all of you should be using because
I'm not just going to get people to click
on this on long form like I've done in
this video.
I want people to get this on short form.
So where is it? Here we go.
This one here. One post on Instagram,
652 people, of which 74% click. So
652 people ended up joining my email list
from the lead
magnet. But you go, "Email list?
I thought this was a resource." Listen,
écoutez,
which is French for listen.
I like to call this the Trojan horse
because
although this is pretty good,
it's a bit brief.
I'm not going to sit here and pretend
that that sheet of paper alone is going to
change your life. What I actually do
was I had to create what you wanted so I
could
give you what you need.
So then I went into Google Docs and
I pre-wrote 11 interesting lessons
that you would need about how
to create a perfect landing page.
I then decided once you get that
asset,
I'm going to email you over the next 11
days because I don't just want to
impact your life on one day.
I want to be in your life for a fortnight,
brother.
And you're going to be like, "What?
Every single day, James is turning up,
giving me a bit of no BS advice to help me
with my landing page?" Yes,
because it's not enough to just help you
once.
I want to be there. Uh-uh,
death by a thousand paper cuts.
Because then even if you don't buy
anything I'm selling, you still walk away
with several actionable things you can put
into your business.
And with what have I got now?
34,000 subscribers on the
channel.
If 10% of you buy what I'm selling,
that's $8.5 million.
So it's completely fine
if the majority of people following me
never do business
because I know that out of
that automation of people
that go through that, some are
going to come out the other end
and be like, "Yo, let's do this, bro.
I like what you're doing."
And do you know why the majority of people
join my
mentorship?
Because they look at the ways in
which I maneuver and flank them
to get them to feel compelled to do
business with me.
They go, "Wow,
if I can compel my audience in any way
similar to the way that James
can compel me to do business, this
is the guy for me." Then for some of you,
you
still don't fully understand the impact as
to why we go after
email so much. Let me tell you this.
We actually only launched
that lead magnet less than 11 days ago.
So the majority of people haven't actually
finished the automation.
But Sunday night, just gone,
I wanted to test a new streaming software.
I wanted to actually use Zoom.
I'm not a big fan of Zoom.
I find it complex
and it reminds me of the pandemic.
So I said to my team, "Hey,
can you email everyone in our database?
But let's actually email all the people
that haven't bought anything
and let's tell
them to come on a livestream webinar
and let's just give them an hour of time."
And
one of the lists we hit
were the people that
are currently going through the
automation for the landing page,
and that's actually where the majority of
that
$24,000 of revenue have come from,
the livestream.
It is so imperatively important
that you get people's data
and just bring it
inside your ecosystem. Whether that
is flashing a bit of paper and
content that actually then puts them into
an email autoresponder, whether that's
actually just getting them to join your
email list through some other way or means
or promise or value attract, whether it
is creating a cheaper
offering that brings them inside the
ecosystem, ultimately it doesn't matter.
Because if your email list is small,
you cannot just try things off the cuff to
see how people respond.
You can't promote offers.
You can't do livestreams.
It's just going to make your life
incredibly difficult.
I'm actually going to put all of my lead
magnets into the link in the description
to this video.
That's the only thing I'm going to put in
there.
And I suggest you don't just sign up so I
can sell to you.
You sign up so you can see the exact
process that I use to get
people to do business with me. Now,
if that isn't genius marketing,
I don't know
what is.
If you put your offer for your lead magnet
on this sign and you held it
above your head in the high street,
would people stop you? If yes, crack on.
If no, sort it out.
Enjoy copying my shit because I'm going to
enjoy converting some of you all.
Let's go.
Bash.